Finding Aid for the George P. Johnson Negro Film Collection LSC.1042
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Research Files
  - N
    - Nash, Johnny
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 280-290. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 89-105, Take a Giant Step. (Reel 12)
    - Nash, Luvenia, Frame(s) 292-95. (Reel 6)
    - Nat King Cole Story, Frame(s) 291. (Reel 9)
    - National Colored Film Corporation, Frame(s) 292. (Reel 9)
    - National Council of Arts, Frame(s) 94. (Reel 1)
    - National Negro Foundation of Performing Arts
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 285, The Gun. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 293, The Gun. (Reel 9)
    - National Theatrical Hall of Fame, Frame(s) 2-3, Robert Abrams. (Reel 1)
    - Native Son
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 294-95. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 210-20, Canada Lee. (Reel 7)
    - A Natural Born Gambler, Frame(s) 296, Bert Williams. (Reel 9)
    - The Navigator, Frame(s) 297. (Reel 9)
    - N'Gegwa, Alfred
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 30, Africa Texas Style. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 298. (Reel 9)
    - Neal Consuela
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 302. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 299. (Reel 9)
    - Neal, Frank, Frame(s) 299, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 4)
    - Nealy, Frances, Frame(s) 300, Finian's Rainbow. (Reel 9)
    - Necessity Women, The, Frame(s) 301. (Reel 9)
    - Neeley, Frances, Frame(s) 300. (Reel 9)
    - Negative and Positives, Frame(s) 302. (Reel 9)
    - The Negro, Frame(s) 303. (Reel 9)
    - Negro Actors, Frame(s) 304-406. (Reel 9)
    - Negro Artist Motion Picture Guild
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 572, 578, Jimmy Fields, Fay Fifer. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 72, Wesley, Gale. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 127, Eddie Lynn. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 300, Frances, Neeley. (Reel 9)
    - Negro Authors, Frame(s) 407-17. (Reel 9)
    - Negro Book Dealers, Frame(s) 418-22. (Reel 4)
    - Negro Boxers, Frame(s) 423-26. (Reel 9)
    - Negro Comedie Films, Frame(s) 10, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
    - Negro Comedy Film Company, Frame(s) 427, Ragtime Billy Tucker. (Reel 9)
    - Negro Ensemble
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 289, Moses Gunn; 593, Robert Hooks. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 590-661, Negroes in Theatre. (Reel 9)
    - Negro Heroes from American History, Frame(s) 428a-b. (Reel 9)
    - Negro History, Frame(s) 548-550, Lincoln C. Hilburn. (Reel 5)
    - Negro Marches On
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 582, Holly Pictures Corporation. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 429-30. (Reel 9)
    - Negro News Monthly, Frame(s) 431, Monumental Picture Corporation. (Reel 9)
    - Negro Newspapers
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 323-329, George P. Johnson. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 432. (Reel 9)
    - Negro of Today, Frame(s) 433. (Reel 9)
    - Negro Soldiers, Frame(s) 434. (Reel 9)
    - Negro Theatres, Frame(s) 435-442. (Reel 9)
    - Negro Westerns, Frame(s) 238-39. (Reel 1)
    - Negroes, Frame(s) 443-523. (Reel 9)
    - Negroes in Moving Pictures, Frame(s) 524-571. (Reel 9)
    - Negroes in Radio, Frame(s) 572-73. (Reel 9)
    - Negroes in Theatre, Frame(s) 590-661. (Reel 9)
    - Negroes in Television, Frame(s) 574-589. (Reel 9)
    - Nelson, Felix, Frame(s) 442, Louise Beavers. (Reel 1)
    - Nelson, Oliver, Frame(s) 662. (Reel 9)
    - Nero, Curtis
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 126, Kongo. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 663. (Reel 9)
    - Never So Few, Frame(s) 664. (Reel 9)
    - Never Too Late, Frame(s) 665. (Reel 9)
    - Never Wave at a Wac, Frame(s) 666, Louise Beavers. (Reel 9)
    - New Face in Hell, Frame(s) 667. (Reel 9)
    - New Faces of 1952, Frame(s) 669. (Reel 9)
    - The New Girl, Frame(s) 670. (Reel 9)
    - The New Interns, Frame(s) 671-72. (Reel 9)
    - A New Kind of Love, Frame(s) 673-75, Erroll Garner. (Reel 9)
    - New Lafayette Theatre, Frame(s) 676-80. (Reel 9)
    - New Liberty Studio Film, Frame(s) 681. (Reel 9)
    - New Orleans, Frame(s) 682. (Reel 9)
    - Newborn, Phineas, Frame(s) 14. (Reel 2)
    - Newport Jazz Festival, Frame(s) 267. (Reel 6)
    - Newton, Huey
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 683. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 680. (Reel 10)
    - Next Time I Marry, Frame(s) 684, Mantan Moreland. (Reel 9)
    - Nicholas, Alice, Frame(s) 685, Eagle of the Sea. (Reel 9)
    - Nicholas Brothers
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 568, The Big Broadcast of 1936; 421, Count Basie. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 232, Down Argentine Way. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 687-93. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 463, The Pirate. (Reel 10)
    - Nicholas, Fayard
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 546-550, Lola Falana. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 686. (Reel 9)
    - Nicholas, Harold
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 316, Carolina Blues. (Reel 2)
        See also Nicholas Brothers.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 275-358, Dorothy Dandridge. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 687-693. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 47, Reckless Age. (Reel 11)
    - Nichols, Michelle
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 201. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 618, Mr. Buddwing. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 574,575, bankruptcy; 694-706. (Reel 9)
    - Night Affair, Frame(s) 707. (Reel 9)
    - Night Club Girl, Frame(s) 708, Delta Rhythm Boys. (Reel 9)
    - Night Fall, Frame(s) 709, Al Hibbler. (Reel 9)
    - Night Hunt, Frame(s) 710. (Reel 9)
    - Night of the Quarter Moon, Frame(s) 711-713. (Reel 9)
    - Night Song
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 714. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 65-66, Sweet Love, Bitter. (Reel 12)
    - Night Without Sleep, Frame(s) 715. (Reel 9)
    - Night World, Frame(s) 716, Clarence Muse. (Reel 9)
    - Nine from Little Rock, Frame(s) 717. (Reel 9)
    - Nine Lives, Frame(s) 718, Butterbeans & Susie. (Reel 9)
    - Nitwits, Frame(s) 719, Willie Best. (Reel 9)
    - No Leave of Love, Frame(s) 720, Sugar Chile Robinson. (Reel 9)
    - No Man Walks Alone, Frame(s) 721, Black Like Me. (Reel 9)
    - No Men Allowed, Frame(s) 722, Nellie Lutcher. (Reel 9)
    - No Peace Under the Magnolias, Frame(s) 723. (Reel 9)
    - No Place to Go, Frame(s) 724. (Reel 9)
    - No Strings, Frame(s) 725. (Reel 9)
    - No Sun in Venice, Frame(s) 4, Motion Picture Industry; 726, John Lewis. (Reel 9)
    - No Time for Tears, Frame(s) 727. (Reel 9)
    - No Vietnamese Ever Call Me Nigger, Frame(s) 728-30. (Reel 9)
    - No Way Out
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 731-36. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 755, Mildred J. Smith. (Reel 11)
    - Noah's Ark, Frame(s) 737, Noble Johnson. (Reel 9)
    - Nobody's Children, Frame(s) 738. (Reel 9)
    - Nocho, Lobo, Frame(s) 739-40. (Reel 9)
    - Noel, Hattie, Frame(s) 741. (Reel 9)
    - Noisette, Kathleen
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 401, Daughter of the Congo. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 536-538, The Exile. (Reel 4)
    - None but the Brave, Frame(s) 742-748. (Reel 9)
    - Nooman, Tommy, Frame(s) 749, I Shot Johnny Ringo. (Reel 9)
    - The Noose, Frame(s) 750, George Reed. (Reel 9)
    - Nordman, Marilyn, Frame(s) 751. (Reel 9)
    - Norman Film Company
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 621, The Flying Ace. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 757-58. (Reel 9)
    - Norman, Floyd, Frame(s) 752. (Reel 9)
    - Norman, Maidie, Frame(s) 753-755 (Reel 9)
      (Note: Ms. Norman's films are listed alphabetically)
    - Norris, Edward, Frame(s) 756. (Reel 9)
    - Norris, Edward, Frame(s) 756. (Reel 9)
    - Norsette, Katherine, Frame(s) 536-538, The Exile. (Reel 4)
    - North, Johnny, Frame(s) 759. (Reel 9)
    - North of the Great Divide, Frame(s) 760, Noble Johnson. (Reel 9)
    - North State Film Corporation, Frame(s) 761. (Reel 9)
    - Not As a Stranger, Frame(s) 762, Juanita Moore. (Reel 9)
    - Nothing But a Man, Frame(s) 763-768. (Reel 9)
    - Notorious Elinor Lee, Frame(s) 769. (Reel 9)
    - Now I'll Tell, Frame(s) 770. (Reel 9)
    - Nubreet, Serge, Frame(s) 771, The Titans. (Reel 9)
    - The Numbers, Frame(s) 772. (Reel 9)
    - The Nun's Story, Frame(s) 773-74. (Reel 9)
  - O
    - O-Brien, Florence
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 236, Argus Pictures. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 183, Dixie National Pictures. (Reel 4)
    - Oceans 11, Frame(s) 1-7. (Reel 10)
    - Odd Man Out, Frame(s) 8. (Reel 10)
    - Odds Against Tomorrow, Frame(s) 13-22. (Reel 10)
    - Odetta
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 563, Festival. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 9-12. (Reel 10)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 93, Requiem for a Nun; Frame(s) 448, Sanctuary. (Reel 11)
    - Odongo, Frame(s) 23. (Reel 10)
    - Of Black America, Frame(s) 24. (Reel 10)
    - Of Men and Music, Frame(s) 25-27. (Reel 10)
    - Offley, Hilda, Frame(s) 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
    - Oh Dad, Poor Dad, Mama's Hung You in the Closet, Frame(s) 28. (Reel 10)
    - Oh Men, Oh Women, Frame(s) 29, Roy Glenn. (Reel 10)
    - Oh Sun, Frame(s) 545. (Reel 9)
    - Okay America, Frame(s) 30, Clarence Brooks. (Reel 10)
    - Okunoyama, George, Frame(s) 31. (Reel 10)
    - Old Bones of the River, Frame(s) 18, Robert Adams. (Reel 1)
    - Old-Fashioned Way, Frame(s) 33, Clarence Wilson. (Reel 10)
    - Old Ironsides, Frame(s) 34-36. (Reel 10)
    - Old Timers, Frame(s) 154-155. (Reel 4)
    - Olden, Charles
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 466, Christie Comedies. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 373, Melancholy Dame. (Reel 8)
    - Oliver, Edna Mae, Frame(s) 385, Penquin Pool Murder. (Reel 10)
    - Oliver, King, Frame(s) 160. (Reel 1)
    - Oliver, Thelma
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 644-648, Black Like Me. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 32. (Reel 10)
    - On Such a Night, Frame(s) 37. (Reel 10)
    - On the Avenue, Frame(s) 38, Stepin Fetchit. (Reel 10)
    - On the Spot, Frame(s) 39, Mantan Moreland. (Reel 10)
    - On the Sunny Side of the Street, Frame(s) 40, Billy Daniels. (Reel 10)
    - On the Waterfront, Frame(s) 41, Don Blackman. (Reel 10)
    - On With the Show, Frame(s) 42. (Reel 10)
    - Once a Thief, Frame(s) 43. (Reel 10)
    - Once in a Lifetime, Frame(s) 44, Decan McDaniels. (Reel 10)
    - Once Upon a Time in the West, Frame(s) 45. (Reel 10)
    - One Big Mistake, Frame(s) 46. (Reel 10)
    - One Dark Night, Frame(s) 47. (Reel 10)
    - One-Eyed Jacks, Frame(s) 48, Henry Scott. (Reel 10)
    - One Hundred Dollar Misunderstanding, Frame(s) 49, Eartha Kitt. (Reel 10)
    - One Hundred Rifles, Frame(s) 50-52. (Reel 10)
    - One Hundred Years of Negro Entertainment, Frame(s) 270-272, Ebony. (Reel 7)
    - One Mile from Heaven, Frame(s) 53. (Reel 10)
    - One More Spring, Frame(s) 54, Stepin Fetchit. (Reel 10)
    - One Potato, Two Potato
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 324-332, Bernie Hamilton. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 55-57. (Reel 10)
    - One Round Jones, Frame(s) 58. (Reel 10)
    - One Touch of Venus, Frame(s) 60, Lena Horne. (Reel 10)
    - O'Neal, Frederick
      - unspecified, Frame(s) Anna Lucasta, 121-125. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 220, Anna Lucasta. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 46, Free White & 21. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 61-68. (Reel 10)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 89-105, Take A Giant Step. (Reel 12)
    - O'Neil, Walter, Frame(s) 69, Something of Value. (Reel 10)
    - Onyx Club, The, Frame(s) 95. (Reel 3)
    - Operation KO, Frame(s) 70. (Reel 10)
    - Operation Mad Ball, Frame(s) 71. (Reel 10)
    - Operation Paradise, Frame(s) 72. (Reel 10)
    - Operator 13, Frame(s) 73. (Reel 10)
    - Orfeu Negro, Frame(s) 74. (Reel 10)
    - The Orioles, Frame(s) 254, Cab Calloway. (Reel 2)
    - The Oscar, Frame(s) 75. (Reel 10)
    - O'Shaughnessy's Boy, Frame(s) 76, Clarence Muse. (Reel 10)
    - Otello
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 605-661, Negroes in Theatre. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 77-80. (Reel 10)
    - Otis, Ted, Frame(s) 81. (Reel 10)
    - Our Christianity and Nobody's Children, Frame(s) 82. (Reel 10)
    - Our Colored Boys in Action Over There, Frame(s) 84. (Reel 10)
    - Our Colored Fighters
      - unspecified, Frame(s) Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 83. (Reel 10)
    - Our Gang
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 435, Stymie Beard; 583, Elmo Billing. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 17-20, Allen Haskins (Farina) 21, Mango. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 85-86. (Reel 10)
    - Our Very Own, Frame(s) 87, James Edwards. (Reel 10)
    - Our Virgin Islands, Frame(s) 88. (Reel 10)
    - Out of Sight, Frame(s) 89, Dobie Gray. (Reel 10)
    - Outlet - A Western Monthly, Frame(s) 90-170. (Reel 10)
    - The Out-of-Towners, Frame(s) 171, Jeanne Arnold. (Reel 10)
    - Out Past on the Nile, Frame(s) 172. (Reel 10)
    - The Outsider, Frame(s) 173. (Reel 10)
    - Over the Goal, Frame(s) 174. (Reel 10)
    - Ovontie, Frame(s) 175, Gaillard Trio. (Reel 10)
    - Owens, Virgil
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 50; 483. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 265. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 176. (Reel 10)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 353-363, Rosebud Film Company. (Reel 11)
    - Owomogela, Oyekan, Frame(s) 177. (Reel 10)
    - Ox Bow Incident, Frame(s) 178, Leigh Whipper. (Reel 10)
  - P
    - P.J., Frame(s) 473-74. (Reel 10)
    - Pace, Harry H.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 198-202, Cosmopolitan Pictures. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 307-443, George P. Johnson. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 290, Pacific Coast News Bureau. (Reel 10)
    - Pace, Jean, Frame(s) 8. (Reel 2)
    - Pace, Judy
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 276, Cotton Comes to Harlem; 294, The Candy Web. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 685, Fortune Cookie. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 10, Redd Foxx. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 179-195. (Reel 10)
    - Pace Phonograph Company, Frame(s) 151. (Reel 3)
    - Pacha, La, Frame(s) 196. (Reel 10)
    - Pacific Coast News Bureau, Frame(s) 197-303. (Reel 10)
    - Page, Harrison, Frame(s) 304. (Reel 10)
    - Page, Hot Lips, Frame(s) 502-05. (Reel 5)
    - Paige, Leroy (Satchel), Frame(s) 305-318. (Reel 10)
    - Paisan, Frame(s) 319. (Reel 10)
    - Paper Lion, Frame(s) 320. (Reel 10)
    - Paradise Island, Frame(s) 505, Negro entertainers. (Reel 4)
    - Pardon Me Sir, But Is My Eye Hurting your Elbow?, Frame(s) 321. (Reel 10)
    - Parham, Tiny, Frame(s) 629-672, Footlite Magazine. (Reel 4)
    - Paris Blues, Frame(s) 322-329. (Reel 10)
    - Paris Sings Forever, Frame(s) 330, Walter Bryant. (Reel 10)
    - Parker, Charlie
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 400-429, Charles, Ray. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 499, Negro entertainer. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 569, Billie Holliday. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 65-66, Sweet Love, Bitter. (Reel 12)
    - Parker, Delores
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 32, House of Strangers. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 331. (Reel 10)
    - Parker, Dorothy
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 174. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 180, Golden Goose. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 332. (Reel 10)
    - Parker, Frank, Jr., Frame(s) 333. (Reel 10)
    - Parks, Gordon
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 269, 283. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 613, Flavio; 619, Joel Fluellen. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 212, Bobby Goss. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 382. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 334-362. (Reel 10)
    - Parole Fixer, Frame(s) 363, Louise Beavers. (Reel 10)
    - Parrish, Frame(s) 364. (Reel 10)
    - Parrish, John, Frame(s) 442, Louise Beavers. (Reel 1)
    - The Party, Frame(s) 365, The Blossoms. (Reel 10)
    - Patch, Frame(s) 366. (Reel 10)
    - Patch of Blue, Frame(s) 367-370. (Reel 10)
    - Patent Leather Kid, Frame(s) 371. (Reel 10)
    - Patrick, E., Frame(s) 163-165, The $10,000 Trail. (Reel 12)
    - The Patsy, Frame(s) 372, Malcolm Hayes. (Reel 10)
    - Patterson, Floyd, Frame(s) 373. (Reel 10)
    - Patterson, Warren
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 26, Boy, What a Girl. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
    - Patton, John, Frame(s) 385. (Reel 1)
    - Patton, Jonella, Frame(s) 626, Foolish Lives. (Reel 4)
    - Patton, Marguerite, Frame(s) 626, Foolish Lives. (Reel 4)
    - Paul, Betsy, Frame(s) 442, Louise Beavers. (Reel 1)
    - Paul, Ike, Frame(s) 392-562, Oscar Micheaux. (Reel 8)
    - Pawnbroker, Frame(s) 374-76. (Reel 10)
    - Payne, Benny, Frame(s) 367-381, Billy Daniels. (Reel 3)
    - Payne, Jimmy, Frame(s) 377. (Reel 10)
    - Payton, Lew
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 150, Lady from Kentucky. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 2, Racing Lady. (Reel 11)
    - Peaceable Lane, Frame(s) 378. (Reel 10)
    - Peacock, Leslie T., Frame(s) 73-74, Reformation. (Reel 11)
    - Peacock Photoplay, Frame(s) 379. (Reel 10)
    - The Peanut Man, Frame(s) 380. (Reel 10)
    - Pearls of Pauline, Frame(s) 397. (Reel 10)
    - Pearson, Johnny, Frame(s) 497. (Reel 2)
    - Peck's Bad Boy, Frame(s) 381, Gertrude Howard. (Reel 10)
    - Peck's Bad Boy with a Circus, Frame(s) 382, Louise Beavers. (Reel 10)
    - Peggy and Pierre, Frame(s) 383. (Reel 10)
    - Pendulum, Frame(s) 384, Isabel Sanford. (Reel 10)
    - Penn, Jane, Frame(s) 386. (Reel 10)
    - Pennies from Heaven, Frame(s) 387, Louis Armstrong. (Reel 10)
    - Pennima, Richard
      see Little Richard
    - Penguin Pool Murder, Frame(s) 385. (Reel 10)
    - Penrod
      - unspecified, Frame(s) Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 389-91, Ernest & Florence Morrison; 393, Leon Perdue. (Reel 10)
    - Pennsylvania Guard, Frame(s) 7. (Reel 2)
    - Pepe, Frame(s) 392. (Reel 10)
    - Perdue, Leon, Frame(s) 393. (Reel 10)
    - Perez, Raoul, Frame(s) 394. (Reel 10)
    - Perfect Dreamer, The, Frame(s) 395. (Reel 10)
    - The Performers, Frame(s) 396. (Reel 10)
    - Perils of Pauline, Frame(s) 400, Carl Byrd. (Reel 10)
    - Perils of the Jungle, Frame(s) 398, Ernest Wilson. (Reel 10)
    - Perry, Lincoln Theodore
      See Stepin Fetchit
    - Perry, Steve, Frame(s) 399. (Reel 10)
    - Personality Kid, Frame(s) 400, Clarence Muse. (Reel 10)
    - Pershing's Crusaders, Frame(s) 9, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
    - Persoff, Nehemiah, Frame(s) 495, Hell Spills Over. (Reel 5)
    - Pete Kelly's Blues, Frame(s) 401-404. (Reel 10)
    - Peter P. Jones Film Company, Frame(s) 405-6. (Reel 10)
    - Peters, Brock
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 265, Godfrey Cambridge. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 407-422 * (Reel 10)
        (Note Mr. Peters' films are listed alphabetically)
    - Peters, Doug, Frame(s) 423, The 10 Commandments. (Reel 10)
    - Peters, Edith
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 677, Blood and the Cook. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 368, Carthage in Flames. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 72, Operation Paradise; 374-76, Pawnbroker; 424-26. (Reel 10)
    - Peters, Mattie, Frame(s) 427, Louisiana. (Reel 10)
    - Peters Sisters, Frame(s) 428-32. (Reel 10)
    - Peters, Teddye, Frame(s) 629-672, Footlite Magazine. (Reel 4)
    - Peters, Virginia, Frame(s) 433. (Reel 10)
    - Peterson, Caleb, Frame(s) 434. (Reel 10)
    - Peterson, Lenka, Frame(s) 644-48, Black Like Me. (Reel 1)
    - Peterson, Lew
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 619, Joel Fluellen. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 435. (Reel 10)
    - Peterson, Louis, Frame(s) 89-105, Take A Giant Step. (Reel 12)
    - Peterson, Monica, Frame(s) 436-37. (Reel 10)
    - Peterson, Oscar
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 602, Nat King Cole. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 268. (Reel 6)
    - Petry, Ann, Frame(s) 14; 683, Mary E. Vroman. (Reel 12)
    - Pettiford, Oscar, Frame(s) 95. (Reel 3)
    - Petway, Bruce, Frame(s) 111-114, Andlauer Productions. (Reel 1)
    - Phantom of Crestwood, Frame(s) 438, Clarence Wilson. (Reel 10)
    - Phillips, Dorothy, Frame(s) 440-43. (Reel 10)
    - Phillips, Ferman, Frame(s) 444. (Reel 10)
    - Phillips, Hilton, Frame(s) 132-33, Ingagi. (Reel 6)
    - Phillips, Roy, Frame(s) 439, The Learning Tree. (Reel 10)
    - Picasso Summer, The, Frame(s) 445. (Reel 10)
    - Pickaninny, Frame(s) 446. (Reel 10)
    - Pickens, Albertine
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 327-717, Lincoln Motion Picture Company; 597, Law of Nature. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 447-48. (Reel 10)
    - Pickett, Bill, Frame(s) 449-454. (Reel 10)
    - Pictorial Film Company, Frame(s) 455. (Reel 10)
    - Piedro de Toque, Frame(s) 456. (Reel 10)
    - Pierson, Don, Frame(s) 476-77, Hearts of the Woods. (Reel 5)
    - Pillow to Post, Frame(s) 457. (Reel 10)
    - Pilot, Beatrice, Frame(s) 469-475, Hearts in Dixie. (Reel 5)
    - Pin-Up Girl, Frame(s) 460. (Reel 10)
    - Pink, Janice, Frame(s) 458. (Reel 10)
    - Pinky, Frame(s) 459. (Reel 10)
    - Pioneer National Newsreel, Frame(s) 461. (Reel 10)
    - Piper, Delores, Frame(s) 462. (Reel 10)
    - The Pirate, Frame(s) 463, Nicholas Brothers. (Reel 10)
    - Pirates of Tortuga, Frame(s) 464. (Reel 10)
    - Pistol Packin' Mama, Frame(s) 465, Nat King Cole Trio. (Reel 10)
    - Pistolerus, Frame(s) 466. (Reel 10)
    - Pittman, Elana, Frame(s) 467-472. (Reel 10)
    - Pittman, Portia W., Frame(s) 498. (Reel 9)
    - A Place in Sun, Frame(s) 475, Frances Friver. (Reel 10)
    - Planet of the Apes, Frame(s) 476, Jeff Burton. (Reel 10)
    - The Platters
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 39-45, Ernie Freeman; 611, Zola Taylor marries. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 477-79. (Reel 10)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 332, Rock All Night. (Reel 11)
    - Pleasant, Henry, Frame(s) 266, Ties of Blood. (Reel 12)
    - Pofkin, Harry M., Frame(s) 641. (Reel 10)
    - Point Blank, Frame(s) 480-2. (Reel 10)
    - Poitier, Sidney
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 4-14, Academy Awards; 59-61; 94, National Council of Arts; 465, 470, 503, Harry Belafonte. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 263-74, G. Cambridge; 329. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 362-69, L. Hansberry; 442, T. Hatton. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 304. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 483-637 *. (Reel 10)
    - Polk, Oscar
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 236, Cabin in the Sky. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 187-99, Gone With The Wind 253, Green Pastures. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 638. (Reel 10)
    - Pollard, Fritz, Frame(s) 639. (Reel 10)
    - Poncomania, Frame(s) 640. (Reel 10)
    - Poree, Anita
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 733-36. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 669. (Reel 10)
    - Porgy and Bess
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 254, Cab Calloway. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 268, Barbara Dumas; 272, T. Duncan. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 642-68. (Reel 10)
    - Pork Chop Hill, Frame(s) 670-71. (Reel 10)
    - Port-au-Prince, Frame(s) 672, Breno Mello. (Reel 10)
    - Portman, Eric
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 237, The Assignment. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 305, The Cardinal. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 43, Deadfall. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 5, The 49th Parallel. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 30, House of Cards. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 377, Men of Two Worlds. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 258, The Naked Edge. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 875, The Spy with Cold Nose. (Reel 11)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 862, The Whisperers. (Reel 12)
    - Portrait of Jason, Frame(s) 673, Shirley Clark. (Reel 10)
    - Portrait of Jennie, Frame(s) 674. (Reel 10)
    - Pot Luckless, Frame(s) 674b. (Reel 10)
    - POW, Frame(s) 375, Earle Hyman. (Reel 10)
    - Powell, Adam Clayton, Jr.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 499, Harry Belafonte. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 107, 116, Jim Brown; 561 Nat King Cole. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 676. (Reel 10)
    - Priest for St. Rose, The, Frame(s) 701. (Reel 10)
    - Prince of His Race, Frame(s) 703-05. (Reel 10)
    - Prince of Players, Frame(s) 706, Bill Walker. (Reel 10)